<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Emilio Blacksmith Blog</title>
    <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Emilio Blacksmith Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 16:29:07 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 17:44:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Testing out my first blog post, this website was developed using HUGO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Music Genre Every 3 Days</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/a-music-genre-every-3-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 16:29:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/a-music-genre-every-3-days/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a challenge, but why Howdy, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I wrote a blog post, there&amp;rsquo;s plenty that I want to talk with you, but this post ain&amp;rsquo;t about that, it&amp;rsquo;s a different type of post focused towards a small thing that I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about, and just now starting to apply it on my day to day basis.
I&amp;rsquo;ve felt very sad, a lot of things have happen, but a key takeaway that might be important for this precise project, is the feeling of not being enough, feeling like I&amp;rsquo;m boring and that I don&amp;rsquo;t bring any value to my relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pausing My Project</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/pausing-my-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 20:38:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/pausing-my-project/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start Life is cyclical, sometimes we define different plans, different paths to follow, those can be set by someone else, or can be chosen by ourselves. But we set different plans for ourselves as time flies, and this world keeps us guessing for what&amp;rsquo;s next. Ever since I started this path as a game developer, I set my destiny somewhat high up, in 2020, I decided that I was going to be a gamedev youtuber, I followed that path ever since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Gamedev to Webdev Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/from-gamedev-to-webdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:55:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/from-gamedev-to-webdev/</guid>
      <description>Why Am I switching to becoming a Web Developer? I&amp;rsquo;m a game developer, I&amp;rsquo;ve been a game developer ever since 2017, I started in a very early stage, by doing simple projects here and there, by following a ton of tutorials, and since 2021, I started to get more and more interested into becoming a web developer. I&amp;rsquo;ve found joy in developing websites, and tools with this websites. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insecurities</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/insecurities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 20:34:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/insecurities/</guid>
      <description>It happens, even to the best of all of us&amp;hellip; Life is interesting sometimes, it bless you with people, it bless you with time, it bless you with commodity, it bless you with many things to be grateful for. I&amp;rsquo;m grateful I&amp;rsquo;m not going to lie, life is beautiful, but no matter what, there days, just like this, where life makes you think, makes you analyze your relationships, your passions, your projects, your path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Trick Behind Productivity</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/the-trick-behind-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:13:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/the-trick-behind-productivity/</guid>
      <description>What is Productivity? You have probably felt the same, you&amp;rsquo;re exploring different youtube videos about the topic of self improvement, productivity and how to use your time efficiently to make more things, get more money, make your own business, etc etc.
The truth is that the current digital era has taught us that there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility of becoming better, becoming more productive doing X, Y an Z actions. Learn 10 different tips and tricks about how to become more productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Plan</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/my-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 14:35:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/my-plan/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s understand the WHY&amp;rsquo;s? Howdy, welcome to a new small post. I understand this might not even be an interesting topic to read about, because it is entirely just about me, myself and my plans ahead in this wonderful and interesting life. If this is the first time you read a post of mine, this might not be the best of introductions, so go ahead and try others instead, like the recent post I made regarding Unity&amp;rsquo;s decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Unity Engine</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/goodbye_unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 17:20:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/goodbye_unity/</guid>
      <description>Dear Unity Unity is a game engine that I&amp;rsquo;ve used in the past, and I&amp;rsquo;m willing to say was my dear tool to make most of my ideas a reality in the gamedev world, I created my first videogame with it, and it is allocated in a very special place in my heart, I started using this game engine since 2014, not full time obviously, but it was absolutely a game changer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personalizing my Terminal Environment</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/personalizing-terminals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:57:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/personalizing-terminals/</guid>
      <description>Why did I Personalized my Terminal? Howdy random stranger, welcome to another blog post, in today&amp;rsquo;s topic I&amp;rsquo;m explaining a bit of what I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this entire weekend, lmao.
But before I kinda explain a bit about the personalization of my personal terminal, let me explain a bit about how I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the terminal before, and my settings before this whole mess lmao.
The Process&amp;hellip; Before. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a simple dev, the closest thing of using the terminal it has been more related to that one time last year when I used Linux actively to learn deeper in terms of Web Development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Hello, World!</title>
      <link>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/real_hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:37:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://emilioblacksmith.github.io/Blog/posts/real_hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my Blog 🤠 Hello, howdy, how you doing, my name is Emilio Blacksmith (real name Emilio Herrera, BUT, Herrera in english is Blacksmith).
I&amp;rsquo;m a Developer, I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing Game Development since 2017. But wasn&amp;rsquo;t till 2021 where I started a youtube channel focused on game development tutorials with tools like the unity game engine, then in 2022 I started to lean towards doing more entertainment content based on development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
